
const Questions = [
    {
        question: "Nocent",
        answers: {
            a: "Having a possibility to cause harm",
            b: "Having a potential to do good",
            c: "Having a very kind mind",
            d: "He is very bad"
        },
        correctAnswer: "a"
    },

    {
        question: "Refute",
        answers: {
            a: "To approve",
            b: "To disprove",
            c: "To reduce",
            d: "To increase"
        },
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },

    {
        question: "Munificient",
        answers: {
            a: "Extremely arrogant",
            b: "Unbelievably rich",
            c: "Very dangerous",
            d: "Extremely kind or generous"
        },
        correctAnswer: "d"
    },

    {
        question: "Sumptuousity",
        answers: {
            a: "The state of being poor",
            b: "The ability to do difficult works",
            c: "The quality possessed by expensive things",
            d: "The state of being exceedingly large"
        },
        correctAnswer: "c"
    },

    {
        question: "Impudence",
        answers: {
            a: "A state of being rude or imppertinent",
            b: "A state of being polite",
            c: "An ability to influence people",
            d: "A state of being generous"
        },
        "answer": "a"
    },

    {
        question: "Impertinent",
        answers: {
            a: "Having no relevance to the current matter",
            b: "Useful to the matter at hand",
            c: "Not dangerous",
            d: "Dangerous"
        },
        correctAnswer: "a"
    },

    {
        question: "Laconic",
        answers: {
            a: "Wordy",
            b: "Detailed",
            c: "Brief and to the point",
            d: "Repetitive"
        },
        correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "Castigation",
        answers: {
            a: "Beating as punishment",
            b: "Verbal punishment or severe scolding",
            c: "A state of being nice",
            d: "An ability to help others"
        },
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "Love",
        answers: {
            a: "it describes thing that is dangerous",
            b: "The Terminator",
            c: "Waluigi, obviously",
            d: "Spiderman"
        },
        correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "Instigate",
        answers: {
            a: "To bring to an end",
            b: "To halt",
            c: "To incite or cause",
            d: "To move"
        },
        correctAnswer: "c"
    }, 
    {
        question: "Tumultuous?",
        answers: {
            a: "Characterized by unrest, disorder or insubordination",
            b: "Very calm",
            c: "Too dangerous",
            d: "Improving with calmness"
        },
        correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
         question: "Sycophant",
         answers: {
            a: "A person who pleases someone for personal gain",
            b: "A person who helps honestly",
            c: "A man who hates woman",
            d: "A person who hates money"
        },
        correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of our Oga in the computer lab",
        answers: {
            a: "Rasheed",
            b: "Blessing",
            c: "Kenny",
            d: "Mubarak"
        },
        correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the Nigerian in #100 note?",
        answers: {
            a: "Awolowo",
            b: "Tafawa Balewa",
            c: "Nnamdi Kanu",
            d: "St. Kenny"
        },
        correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the principal of ST. Anthony?",
        answers: {
            a: "Mrs Afolayan",
            b: "Mrs Kuranga",
            c: "Funmilayo R. Kuti",
            d: "St. Kenny"
        },
        correctAnswer: "b"
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "Who is Emmanuel?",
        answers: {
            a: "A student",
            b: "A lawyer",
            c: "A doctor",
            d: "A scientist"
        },
        correctAnswer: "d"
    }
];
